35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 4 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ancient building], 12
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ancient building [Parthenon, Greece]], 13
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ancient building [Parthenon, Greece]], 14
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: City, mountains behind it], 15
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Anicent building], 16
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Anicent building], 17
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Building near ocean], 18
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ancient ruins], 19
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Man standing at bottom of steps to ancient ruins], 20
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 5 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: City near ocean, mountains in background], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Sailboat on ocean], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Harbor], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: City near ocean, mountains in background], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Dock, boats out on water], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Dock, boats out on water], 6
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Boats on water], 7
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing by a woman sitting on a camel, pyramid in background], 8
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: City near ocean], 9
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing by a woman sitting on a camel, pyramids in background], 10
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing by a woman sitting on a camel, pyramids in background], 11
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing by a woman sitting on a camel, pyramids and sphynx in background], 12
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman riding on a camel, pyramids at her right], 13
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman sitting on camel in front of pyramid], 14
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Man in Egyptian garb sitting on camel in front of pyramid], 15
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman riding on camel in front of pyramid], 16
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Man in Egyptian garb sitting on camel in front of pyramid], 17
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Person riding on [Trying to control a] camel in front of pyramid], 18
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Man riding on camel in front of pyramid], 19
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Person riding [Trying to control a] camel in front pyramid], 20
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 6 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ancient ruins, mountains in background], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Ancient ruins, mountains in background], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: View of city], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Buildings on rolling hills], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: A bell tower], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: View of city], 6
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: White building with statue of a man in front], 7
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: An alleyway], 8
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: White building with statue of a man in front], 9
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Stretch of fountain and building at the end], 10
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Building with a fountain in front of it], 11
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: The Taj Mahal], 12
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of people in Arabic garb], 13
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Building with a fountain in front of it], 14
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman standing in front of steps, smiling], 15
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of women in Arabic garb], 16
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman standing in front of steps, smiling], 17
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of people in Arabic garb], 18
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: People walking by], 19
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: People walking by], 20
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 7 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman balancing a basket on her head ], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman balancing a basket on her head ], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: People walking down a street in Arabic garb], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Plants], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: View of ancient building], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Plants], 6
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas and woman standing next to natives with faces painted red], 7
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Crowd of children standing around flags], 8
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a woman's profile], 9
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman standing between two native men], 10
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas and woman talking to two natives], 11
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas and woman standing next to natives with faces painted red], 12
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas and woman standing next to natives with faces painted red], 13
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas and woman talking to two natives], 14
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman next to four natives], 15
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing next to naitve man his child, native man holding an artifact], 16
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a woman's profile], 17
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing next to native man with an elaborate headdress], 18
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing next to native man with an elaborate headdress], 19
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing next to native man with an elaborate headdress], 20
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 8 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large crowd of people outside of a building], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman standing next to native woman], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman standing next to native woman], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman talking with native woman], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Woman standing next to native woman], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large crowd of people outside of building], 6
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large crowd of people outside of building], 7
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large crowd of people outside of building], 8
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large crowd of people outside of building], 9
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large crowd of people outside of building], 10
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: People watching crowd of other people], 11
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large crowd of people outside of building], 12
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 13
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Lowell Thomas standing next to two native women with painted faces], 14
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance, large crowd of people], 15
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance, large crowd of people], 16
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large crowd of people on a hill], 17
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: [Natives marching in a formation down a road] Large crowd of people on a hill], 18
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: [Large crowd of people on a hill] outside a building], 19
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: [Large crowd of people outside a building], 20
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 9 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Line of natives marching down a road], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Line of natives marching down a road], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives standing in formation], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 6
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 7
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives standing in formation], 8
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 9
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 10
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 11
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 12
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 13
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 14
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 15
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives putting on a performance], 16
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Large crowd of people outside of building], 17
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 10 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: One native painting another native's face red], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives standing together], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of children sitting on ground with various fruits and vegetables laid in front of them], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Two native people standing and holding spears], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Crowd of natives], 6
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Some natives with painted faces, sitting in front of a hut], 7
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives putting on a performance], 8
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives putting on a performance], 9
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of three native men], 10
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native man leaning against a sign], 11
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Some natives furnishing some objects], 12
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Natives marching in a formation], 13
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: View of a city], 14
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man holding a spear], 15
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives], 16
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives with headdresses and spears, walking], 17
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives with headdresses and spears, talking], 18
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Two natives with painted faces and headdresses], 19
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Two natives with painted faces and headdresses], 20
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Two natives with painted faces and headdresses], 21
  - Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea], circa 1963; 11 (Box 1590)
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives], 1
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Two natives standing together], 2
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man's face], 3
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives with headdresses and spears], 4
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives with headdresses and spears], 5
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Group of natives with headdresses], 6
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native man with a headdress standing next to a little boy], 7
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native man with a headdress standing next to a little boy], 8
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Native man holding a spear], 9
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man wearing a headdress], 10
    - [Carousel number 33 [Lowell Thomas and Christl Thalhammer tour the world, including Greece, Egypt and New Guinea]: Close-up of a native man wearing a headdress], 11